<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>b3313-v1.0</identifier>
  <mediatype>software</mediatype>
  <collection>open_source_software</collection>
  <collection>community</collection>
  <creator>Christopher Rios Lillo et al.</creator>
  <date>2024-02-04</date>
  <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;APRIL 2ND, 2025 UPDATE:&lt;/u&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Currently B3313 Unabandoned A3 is in the works and will be released soon on a specific release date, which is as of now there's no estimated release date yet. 1.0.3 is cancelled tho.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;© 1996 Nintendo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;© 2021-2025 Christopher Rios Lillo and his team&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;© 2023-2025 B3313 Unabandoned Team (TheGreatestRoman, &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chlorobyte, &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Emax64 &amp;amp; Thunder (WOB music patch, A2 &amp;amp; A3), Floralys (A2 &amp;amp; A3))&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;⚠️ WARNING - SEIZURES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Some people may have seizures triggered by light flashes or patterns like those in video games.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stop playing if you experience altered vision, muscle or eye twitching, loss of awareness or disorientation.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Will you play the game, or will the game play you?”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;—&lt;b&gt;B3313 official slogan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is the binary, most-downloaded RHDC hack (w/ over 100k downloads!) that is based on the Internal Plexus concept, played by most streamers and content creators alike, featuring scrapped features and stages from the beta and the SM64 iceberg, mixed and matched together to create uncanny experiences. B13 and the Motos Factory demos contains only a few areas, with the example being the titular course from the Motos Factory demo, also known as the 'Motos Factory'. Real-time clock are also included as well since the Motos Factory demo, just like the 'lost-demo' video that's seen on the SM64 classified YouTube series, and the Japan-only release of Animal Crossing: Population Growing on the N64, as well as the changes depending on the time of the system clock. Has references to the other hacks as well, example being The City, being based that one area from Gamma64.&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 Hellsheet, good source for B3313-related information: &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1HhX6ldAGSTQxWO--DQ28KYCAQeOZw8FzfvuUC8fUG6g/edit?usp=sharing" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1HhX6ldAGSTQxWO--DQ28KYCAQeOZw8FzfvuUC8fUG6g/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT IS SUPER MARIO B3313? (by BrettWils; spoiler-free official 1.0 video): &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fn1f9LQ9EWQ" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fn1f9LQ9EWQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 1.0 (official) STAR/AREA LIST: &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1VChVOpO7mSJwKBxXaFOeViv9mDiRXXmsQALgS9gFqqc/edit?usp=sharing" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1VChVOpO7mSJwKBxXaFOeViv9mDiRXXmsQALgS9gFqqc/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;OFFICIAL 1.0 OVERVIEW: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bnm_7Vsp45o" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bnm_7Vsp45o&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;ACHIEVEMENTS (updated for the latest official release): &lt;a href="https://retroachievements.org/game/17500" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://retroachievements.org/game/17500&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;FANDOM WIKI: &lt;a href="https://b3313.fandom.com/" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://b3313.fandom.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;MIRAHEZE WIKI (official, wip): &lt;a href="https://b3313.info/" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://b3313.info/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 FOR DUMMIES (AND STREAMERS) (W.I.P; latest official release is currently v1.0.2, though the actual latest is v1.0.2 hotfix 3): &lt;/b&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ee"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://b3313guide.com" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://b3313guide.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;UA = Unabandoned&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Archived for preservation purposes.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;LEGAL DISCLAIMER: &lt;/b&gt;This project is NOT, in any way associated with/or endorsed by Nintendo, or its subsidiaries/contracted developers at all. It is a non-profit ROM hack that was created by project lead Christopher and the B3313 team. Please support Nintendo by purchasing their current products, services and games, and even the Nintendo Switch Online + Expansion Pack subscription just to play Super Mario 64 on the Nintendo Switch, and for more information on Nintendo, their properties and their history, look forward to upcoming Nintendo titles as well as pre-ordering it after pre-orders for the upcoming title begins.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The tweaked versions are recommended since all it does is to fix some stuff to make it work on LLE video plugins (and on real hardware if it's B13). Do not get the untweaked versions, as these versions doesn't do anything like the tweaked versions and can cause problems if ran through LLE video plugins (and the N64 hardware; B13 only).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Starting with B3313 v0.9 and Unabandoned releases, as both the tweaked and the untweaked versions are identical to each other, these are now all placed onto its root directory of this item, as you'll have the full uninterrupted B3313 experience without worrying about any LLE problems.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The many official B3313 v1.0 releases with some Unabandoned tweaks is also included here, being fan-patches with "crash fixes", star count fixes like the red stars not adding to the counter at all, Nighttime Castle Grounds character switches, fixed difficulty scaling Goombas, and the red star progression tweaked to be more like Unabandoned. (oh and also a surprise; the old ones doesn't have those new changes, &amp;amp; versions from 1.0.2 onwards, plus I don't think the tweaked v1.0.1 TRUE final hotfix 3 &amp;amp; 4 is gonna be updated anyway)&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;It's recommended to get the latest B3313 v1.0.2 third hotfix release that isn't a fan patch since that's the most definitive version you're looking for and is more stable than all of the previous B3313 v1.0 releases, however it's not compatible with real hardware so for real hardware players, get Unabandoned A2 1st Anniversary instead, which is just v0.9 but with a higher star count than the official v1.0, new courses and a working but different ending.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;There are some places officially associated with Chris with stuff saying that you should not support the Unabandoned build, I mean I can't ultimately stop you from playing but, at the very least please refrain from mentioning even one bit of Unabandoned at all in, again &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;some places officially associated with Chris&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;. (the ones with Chlorobyte and TheGreatestRoman being banned for making Unabandoned exist and stuff) &lt;u&gt;However, as of now &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;—&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt; all the drama related to Unabandoned are over.&lt;/u&gt; &lt;/b&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-peace.PNG" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Unabandoned RHDC star layout and normal + RHDC official v1.0-TRUE v1.0.1 hotfix 3 &amp;amp; v1.0.2 star layout is included as well for archival purposes. (and the unofficial official v1.0 star layouts)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;You need an original US ROM of Super Mario 64 in order to patch &amp;amp; play this. Expansion pak is required, and to properly emulate the "AI" correctly, use ParaLLel as the default video plugin for this ROM hack. If it struggles to run/crashes, use Angrylion. If it still struggles/crashes, use GLideN64 w/ frame buffer. GLideN64 is also a recommended video plugin for (homebrewed) Nintendo Switch players.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;u style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;PC users only:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;You'll also need Parallel Launcher as the recommended emulator in order to, again, play this. If you're a Project64 user, &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/view/shurislibrary/luna-project64" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;get Luna's Project64 from Shuri's Library. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;Project64 Legacy v1.6.4 (latest version) also works with this hack.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Android users only (and Nintendo Switch; maybe PC):&lt;/u&gt; &lt;/b&gt;From B3313 Unabandoned's RHDC page: 96 MB ROM! (doesn't apply to versions prior to v0.9, UA A2 1st anniversary &amp;amp; A3) It will only run with Parallel Launcher's ParallelN64 core (not RetroArch's), or custom builds of Mupen swapping a single line of code. For the custom Mupen builds (e.g. mobile users) and an explanation, visit&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ee"&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.chlorobyte.me/2023/mupen_readme/" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://docs.chlorobyte.me/2023/mupen_readme/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;div&gt;(the prebuilt binaries for each platforms -- Windows, Linux, and Android, &amp;amp; the build system does have the RSP DMA vulnerability patched so you shouldn't worry about those, except for the Nintendo Switch; wait, what would the hacker do on a Switch???)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;u style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;N64 users only:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Unplayable, except the tweaked versions of B13, B3313 1.0 Unabandoned A2 1st Anniversary edition &amp;amp; the upcoming A3 release. &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/2NUSzvzIrKE" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;0.9 however works only on a SummerCart64&lt;/a&gt;, but it's too unoptimized. 0.9 run by Meyadin.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;VERSION HISTORY (there's a lot of versions; some sources may not be reliable, also the Discord sources that I've provided are using the GMT+7 timezone, which may show the dates differently than usual):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.2 hotfix 3&lt;/b&gt; (May 11th, 2024) - Same as the second v1.0.2 hotfix release but with a really nasty bug found in Lunar Tower fixed. &lt;b&gt;The actual true final one, and is much more polished than the previous official B3313 v1.0 releases. Latest official release, and as of now I don't think it's getting any official updates anymore after this.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.2hotfix3.PNG" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.2 hotfix 2&lt;/b&gt; (May 9th, 2024) - Same as the first v1.0.2 hotfix release but with bugfixes related to a star in Jolly Roger Bay (beta) &amp;amp; Motos Factory and the Shift&lt;b&gt;ed&lt;/b&gt; Sand Land tree grab thing.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.2hotfix2.PNG" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.2 hotfix 1&lt;/b&gt; (May 8th, 2024) - Same as the original v1.0.2 release but with the empty object crash bug in Shift&lt;b&gt;ed&lt;/b&gt; Sand Land patched out.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.2hotfix1.PNG" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.2&lt;/b&gt; (May 7th, 2024) - 460 stars (433 yellows; the other yellow star is a grand one, 14 reds; all increments the star count, also the other 1 is a grand red star, 13 greens which increments the star count), along with other fixes &amp;amp; tweaks.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.2.PNG" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 TRUE v1.0.1 hotfix 3&lt;/b&gt; (April 23rd, 2024) - Same as the true v1.0.1 hotfix 2 release but with the remaining broken exit warps fixed.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;u&gt;List of broken warps fixed in TRUE v1.0.1 hotfix 3:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- AI Underground (death exit only as there is no star)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- All the places entered via the question mark painting in the Personalization Chamber&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Aquarium Limbo (the course in Crimson Hallway)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Big Blue Skylands (death by damage exit only; you can't die by falling)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Big Boo's Haunted Forest entered via Vanilla Lobby&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Bowser in the Dark World (Shoshinkai) (death exit only)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Delicious Cake entered via Floor 3B&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Eternal Fort (beta) (death exit only)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Mario's Maze&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Tower of the Wing Cap (beta) entered via Challenge Lobby&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-TRUE1.0.1hotfix3.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;&lt;b&gt;image source&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://romhacking.com/hack/b3313-super-mario-64-internal-plexus#9fc57240-bbe7-49db-8f2d-8f83ca567baf_5149b493-8c5e-4872-8b1f-e365c5d4c340" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;&lt;b&gt;website source&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 TRUE v1.0.1 hotfix 2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;(April 20th, 2024) - Same as the true v1.0.1 hotfix 1 release but with the bug where the one painting that doesn't boot back to where you entered + other bugs which was present in TRUE v1.0.1 fixed, and green star adjustments.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-TRUE1.0.1hotfix2.PNG" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 TRUE v1.0.1 hotfix 1 &lt;/b&gt;(April 18th, 2024) - Same as the true v1.0.1 release but with the bug related to the Vanilla Castle Grounds moat door removed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-TRUE1.0.1hotfix1.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 TRUE v1.0.1 &lt;/b&gt;(April 18th, 2024) - Same as the fourth true final hotfix but with fixed warps and QoL improvements. This also removes the debug menu and creates a new bug related to the Vanilla Castle Grounds moat door. &lt;b&gt;I couldn't grab it before TRUE v1.0.1 hotfix came out (I wasn't aware), that's why it's lost media until it was found later by Ren Fuchsfein, who contacted BikdipOnABus to get the lost TRUE v1.0.1 original &amp;amp; first release he has saved in his computer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-TRUE1.0.1.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.1 TRUE final hotfix 4&lt;/b&gt; (March 27th, 2024) - Same as the third true final hotfix but with a single hex edit that fixes the colored Goomba anomaly.&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.1truefinalhotfix4.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.1 TRUE final hotfix 3&lt;/b&gt; (Somewhere between March 15-16th, 2024) - Released without announcement, same as the second true final hotfix but with Randomized Realm Piranha Plant fixes + Chroma Tundra's night music removed as Chroma Tundra is now set to always daytime, which means even if it's nighttime it'll take you into the daytime version instead each time you enter the Chroma Tundra painting. Also includes the chomp gate switch so it's easier to get stars and stuff and fixes softlocks relating to the Chain Chomp and the log.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/B3313-1.0.1-hotfix-TRUEFINAL-3_changelog.png" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;&lt;b&gt;changelog&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.1truefinalhotfix3.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;&lt;b&gt;chris march 16th s&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;ource&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.1 TRUE final hotfix 2&lt;/b&gt; (March 7th, 2024) - Same as the first true final hotfix but with MIPS in the Crimson Hallway you access with the big boo through Plexal Lobby removed.&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This also includes all traces of duplicate courtyard MIPS and fixes a warp pipe's height.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.1truefinalhotfix2.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.1 TRUE final hotfix 1&lt;/b&gt; (March 6th, 2024) - v1.0.1 final hotfix but with crashes fixed, minor changes and QOL improvements.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Still 450 stars but now all 450 stars shows up in-game (424 yellows, 13 reds; all increments star count, 13 greens which increments the star count)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.1truefinalhotfix1.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.1 final hotfix&lt;/b&gt; (February 5th, 2024) - v1.0.1 hotfix but with "all" bugs (well, not all) relating to the game fixed&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.1finalhotfix.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.1 hotfix&lt;/b&gt; (February 5th, 2024) - v1.0.1 but with red star fixes&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-1.0.1hotfix.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0.1&lt;/b&gt; (February 5th, 2024) - v1.0 hotfix but...I'm too lazy to list all the changes in one line myself so here's the hotfix changes:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;MIPS has been removed from Crimson Hallway and Rainbow Highway. He can now only give stars in Uncanny Courtyard, so there's no possibilty of have stars permanently missable. (Aside from hitting the yellow switch, which can still flip those on and off).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Blazing Bullet Factory bob-omb was accidentally left as a duplicate. It has now been made into a unique ID, and three brand new stars were added.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Limitless Lighthouse and Ice-Cold Warzone had their IDs changed as well for technical reasons.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Snowman's Land beta - ice house      01-4        19&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Ice-Cold Warzone          01-5        20&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Melting Magma Mound - top      02-1        24&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Limitless Lighthouse          10-4        91&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Toxic Forest - red coins      10-5        92&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bullet Factory - bob-omb      ExS8 1    192/1&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Steep Green Summit - exit pipe      ExS8 5    196/1&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Other bugs have also been fixed, such as water not appearing in certain areas, and areas reported to cause crashes have been updated. The song in Dire Bubble has been reimported.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(source: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/bnm_7Vsp45o?t=817" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 1.0 (final official release) - General overview + hotfix details on YouTube&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; "The last thing I should probably talk about here is the hotfix that happened a day after release.")&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 hotfix &lt;/b&gt;(February 4th, 2024) - v1.0 but with a bug that, in which you can't swim on the Jolly Roger Coastline patched out&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-hotfix.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 &lt;/b&gt;(February 4th, 2024) - 450 stars (424 yellows, 13 reds; 8 increments star count while 5 doesn't, 13 greens which increments the star count, that leaves 445 to be shown in-game) (oh and also there's the debug menu that was left in this version albeit without text displayed onscreen, stayed until TRUE v1.0.1)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(source: &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tl2kNGwyB60" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;B3313 v1.0 - Release Trailer on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;; the upload date for the video)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned [A3]&lt;/b&gt; (unofficial; no estimated release date yet) - Currently in development, will be added into this archive once it's released. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=adkSW4UCPV8" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;Here is one of the songs from A3, which is Neverending Nightmares, composed by Floralys.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aspcW37EDw0" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;concept&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned [A2 1st Anniversary Edition]&lt;/b&gt; (December 24th, 2024) - Just A2 but greatly optimized, with console compatibility patches and fixed warps.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(source: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=27KEXLMP4ko" style="font-weight:bold;" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;Console compatible B3313 is here! - A2 Anniversary Edition trailer on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;; the upload date for the video)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned Starstruck [A2]&lt;/b&gt; (unofficial; December 10th, 2023) - 471 stars (445 yellows, 13 reds, 13 greens) &lt;b&gt;Latest unofficial release until A3 is released.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned [A1] [Original OST]&lt;/b&gt; (unofficial; October 30th, 2023) - Unabandoned A1 but with music changes reverted, still the same thing though. &lt;b&gt;The old version is the version available at &lt;a href="https://chlorobyte.me/b3313/" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;https://chlorobyte.me/b3313/&lt;/a&gt;, while the new version is the version available at Romhacking.com.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(sources for A1 OG OST &amp;amp; A2: &lt;b&gt;List of Versions - B3313 Wiki&lt;/b&gt;; &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://b3313.fandom.com/wiki/List_of_Versions#Unabandoned_(hotfix_with_wasteofblood_music)" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;A1 OG OST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://b3313.fandom.com/wiki/List_of_Versions#Unabandoned_(Starstruck/A2)" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;A2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned [A1]&lt;/b&gt; (unofficial; August 28th, 2023) - 443 stars (430 yellows, 13 reds)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(source: &lt;font color="#0000ee"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WEdeLBWq9Xs" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;B3313 Unabandoned Hotfix Release on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;; the upload date for the video)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned&lt;/b&gt; (unofficial; July 31st, 2023) - 439 stars (426 yellows, 13 reds)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(source: &lt;font color="#0000ee"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m-Z4q6xJQXs" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;B3313 Unabandoned - The Unofficial v1.0 Fix Release Trailer on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;; the upload date for the video)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B3313 v0.9&lt;/b&gt; (May 29th, 2023) - 426 stars (unfortunately, only 180 can be obtainable, with 7 of them being the real reds and 1 of them being the green)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://archive.org/download/b3313-v1.0/b3313-v1.0_crisproof/crisproof-0.9.PNG" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Motos Factory&lt;/b&gt; (January 13th, 2023) - 20 stars (16 yellows, 1 cyan, 3 reds)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;B13&lt;/b&gt; (July 29th, 2022) - 8 stars&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;(sources for B13 &amp;amp; Motos: &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://romhacking.com/hack/B13--a-small-b3313-1.0-preview-" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;RHDC pages for B13 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://romhacking.com/hack/Motos-Factory" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;and Motos Factory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Thanks to the following people for their contributions to/inspirations in B3313 over the years, as well as crediting the original authors of some stuff included in this archive such as footage and assets (official and unofficial):&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;1.0.3 (cancelled) Dev&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;ChrisRLillo&lt;/b&gt; - Lead developer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cammie Ranshedow&lt;/b&gt; - area and texture design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Curly&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hellstormer&lt;/b&gt; - area design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pellwers&lt;/b&gt; - inspiration, area design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pizza Rolls&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;TheShekinah&lt;/b&gt; - texture design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wimzy&lt;/b&gt; - area design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;The rest of the credits list:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;64History&lt;/b&gt; - The Invasion of Nintendo footage on the "alternate" B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned trailerᵘ&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Alieneer &lt;/b&gt;- Code source (The Junuary Project lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Annie &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Genesis Basement), textures, beta resources (Super Mario 64: Classified, MCMXCVI lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Arthurtilly &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Plexal Lobby post-Abandoned) (Super Mario 64 Randomizer developer, Romhacking.com staff)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;BestLizard&lt;/b&gt; - Area modelsᵘ★ (Slide Into Solitude lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;BikdipOnABus &lt;/b&gt;(Documentation and ID settings)&lt;b&gt;, &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Primarina&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;, Snooplax &amp;amp; VeloxusGaming&lt;/b&gt; - Playing v0.9 early before its release date (May 29th, 2023), albeit different&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bizarre-Smile/The Bob&lt;/b&gt; - Area design&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;BlackJoystick &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Floor 2B)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blakeoramo &lt;/b&gt;- Engine development (Do you love Betah?, MARIO64, Shrek 64 lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bobstar &lt;/b&gt;- Music design (e.g. Bowser's Prison)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;BrettWils&lt;/b&gt; - Creator of the "What is Super Mario B3313?" video&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cavin856 &lt;/b&gt;- Area design, programming (ASM)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charles445&lt;/b&gt; - Programming&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chlorobyte&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;- Engine development, programming (ASM and C code injection), edits on Chris' F3 2022 trailer, B3313 v2.0 (Decomp remake) developer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;ChrisRLillo &lt;/b&gt;- Lead developer, composer, inspiration from LM64 (an early hack of his) (Brutal Agresión creator, Luigi's Mansion 64 lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;CurlyTheDingus &lt;/b&gt;- Area design, animations, some textures (Project Fire-Bubble/Water-Fall lead developer, Mario's Palace runner)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;CyberTanuki&lt;/b&gt; - Area design (e.g., Corrupted Beta Lobby, Ultra Battle Fort)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disco&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dudaw &lt;/b&gt;- Source code, main inspiration for making B3313 and information source (Super Mario 64 Beta Revival Project lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dynalox/Bombachu &lt;/b&gt;- Area design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Emax64&lt;/b&gt; - LUIGI IS FUCKING DEADᵘ (Unabandoned/unofficial official v1.0 Star Display creator, wasteofblood music patch developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Farolicious&lt;/b&gt; - Playtesterᵘ&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Felegg &lt;/b&gt;- Object source (Please Come to the Castle developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;FirstCom&lt;/b&gt; - B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned trailer musicsᵘ&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fłorałys&lt;/b&gt; - Starstruck (a2) patch creator, Unabandoned A3 developer &amp;amp; composerᵘ★&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;FluffaMario &lt;/b&gt;- Player models&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Forest of Illusion&lt;/b&gt; - 1996 Nintendo Company Report beta photos hidden in B3313 v0.9, and digitized N64 pre-release trailer on SpongeToo's second fanmade trailer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gab64 &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Cryptic Hideout)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;GoldYosh&lt;/b&gt; - Unofficial Parallel/Star Manager Star Display layouts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gronoti &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Chroma Tundra) (Super Mario 64: The 4th Floor developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Halo/MariHalo &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Silent Sewers), texture design (e.g. cyan bricks) (Zeta64 developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hornet &lt;/b&gt;- Texture design (paintings, HUD, etc), voice actor for the ROM dumper in the F3 2022 trailer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hyena Chan&lt;/b&gt; - Area design (e.g. Grim Green Forest) (only credited in the B13 RHDC page)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;iProgramInCpp &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Tall, Tall Treetops) (Gamma64, Growalone, Nanoshell lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;jefftastic &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (Super Mario 64: Warped Worlds/His Personalized Copy, sm64.z64, Pizza Delivery 64/Petscop 64 developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jman100&lt;/b&gt; - Creator of B3313 For Dummies (and streamers) (&lt;a href="https://tmo.report/" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;The Mobile Report&lt;/a&gt; owner)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;JoshTheBosh &lt;/b&gt;- Area design, programming (ASM and C code injection), area design, music design, B3313 v2.0 (Decomp remake) lead developer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kaze Emanuar &lt;/b&gt;- Beta star model, featuring Chris' trailer on F3 2022 (albeit short) (Waluigi's Taco Stand 64, Return to Yoshi's Island 64 (upcoming hack) developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kyan Pepper &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Carryboy Farmland)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;LaytonLoztew&lt;/b&gt; - Parallel Star Display layout&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lily &lt;/b&gt;- Programming (ASM)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;MarioMaster810&lt;/b&gt; - SM64 Beta Archive "Ghost theme" Recreation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marionova&lt;/b&gt; - Area and music design inspiration (Breaking the Barrier, Ultra Mario World 64 developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mediafire omega (a.k.a. AleFunky) &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Goomba Town)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mrs_kitty&lt;/b&gt; - Chomp Gate Switch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;N64 Squid/Squidgy Squid&lt;/b&gt; - v0.9 reviewer &lt;a href="https://n64squid.com/b3313/" rel="ugc nofollow"&gt;(see the article here)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;NewSupKaizo55 &lt;/b&gt;- Music design (e.g. Dry Town) + v1.0 release music composer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;NicoSwitch &lt;/b&gt;- Music design (e.g. Plexal Lobby)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;nneuhof&lt;/b&gt; - Recorded E3 1996 footage on the "alternate" B3313 v1.0 Unabandoned trailerᵘ&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;PatCangy &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e,g, Polygonal Chaos)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pengu&lt;/b&gt; - Music designᵘ&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Phil564&lt;/b&gt;ᵘ♪&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pointnclick &lt;/b&gt;- Area design inspiration (e.g. Randomized Realm)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;psi64&lt;/b&gt; - Texture design&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pyro Jay &lt;/b&gt;- Programming, ROM Manager assistance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Quills &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (Mario Can't Remember developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rolly Polly&lt;/b&gt; - Playtesterᵘ, Parallel Star Display layout&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rovert&lt;/b&gt; - Enemy design (SM64: Beyond the Cursed Mirror lead developer, Romhacking.com staff)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;SigmaShield &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (e.g. Solar Tower and Lunar Tower)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;SimpleFlips &lt;/b&gt;- Playing v1.0 early for a special charity event, namely the 'Stream of Conscience for American Heart Association 2024' (Romhacking.com owner)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;someone2639 &lt;/b&gt;- Programming (sUGGOH lead developer, Romhacking.com staff)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;SonicAndMarioGames1985 &lt;/b&gt;- Area design (Dream64 lead developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;SpaceOmega&lt;/b&gt; - Area design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;stalechilibeans/crustian&lt;/b&gt; - Polishing WF models (96flashbacks lead developer)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stanley&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Supercoolmario999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Super Mario 64 Beta Archive&lt;/b&gt; - Area design inspiration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Taxi Yoshi 64&lt;/b&gt; - N64 footage on Chris' F3 2022 trailer (Project Beta 64 developer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;TheGreatestRoman &lt;/b&gt;- Object placement, pasting text (B3313 Wiki creator, map creator, B3313 Unabandoned director)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Preservation Project&lt;/b&gt; - Asset source&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Toriellabella&lt;/b&gt; - B3313 Hellsheet creator&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;TwinLamps/SpongeToo&lt;/b&gt; - Archived this collection&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Thunder&lt;/b&gt;ᵘ♪ (B3313 Unabandoned WOB music patch lead director)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ultra Mario World 64&lt;/b&gt; - Area design inspiration (e.g. Nebula Lobby) and music design inspiration (e.g. Parallel Lobby and Royal Lobby)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Usernamesarespiders &lt;/b&gt;- Area design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;wasteofblood &lt;/b&gt;- Music design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Willisaclown &lt;/b&gt;- Music design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Zany Z-Fight &lt;/b&gt;- Area design, texture design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;And most importantly, thank &lt;b&gt;you&lt;/b&gt; so much for playing B3313!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div&gt;ᵘUnabandoned &amp;amp; A1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;ᵘ♪Unabandoned WOB Music Patch&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;ᵘ★Unabandoned Starstruck &amp;amp; A3&lt;/div&gt;</description>
  <language>eng</language>
  <scanner>Internet Archive HTML5 Uploader 1.7.0</scanner>
  <subject>sm64</subject>
  <subject>nintendo 64</subject>
  <subject>personalized</subject>
  <subject>personalisation</subject>
  <subject>personalization</subject>
  <subject>a.i.</subject>
  <subject>ai</subject>
  <subject>internal castle plexus</subject>
  <subject>build 3313</subject>
  <subject>n64</subject>
  <subject>ultra 64 mario bros.</subject>
  <subject>ultra 64 mario b3313</subject>
  <subject>nintendo ultra 64</subject>
  <subject>shoshinkai '95</subject>
  <subject>spaceworld 1995</subject>
  <subject>spaceworld '95</subject>
  <subject>december 1995</subject>
  <subject>december '95</subject>
  <subject>march 1996</subject>
  <subject>march '96</subject>
  <subject>pre-e3</subject>
  <subject>every copy is personalized</subject>
  <subject>every copy of super mario 64 is personalized</subject>
  <subject>ultra mario bros. 64</subject>
  <subject>ultra mario 64</subject>
  <subject>e3 1996</subject>
  <subject>e3 '96</subject>
  <subject>july 29th, 1995 build</subject>
  <subject>07/29/1995 build</subject>
  <subject>1995/07/29 build</subject>
  <subject>nu64</subject>
  <subject>luigi</subject>
  <subject>l is real 2401</subject>
  <subject>creepypasta</subject>
  <subject>creepy</subject>
  <subject>scary</subject>
  <title>B3313 v1.0 all official and Unabandoned releases &amp; 2 demos</title>
  <uploader>notvillager64@protonmail.com</uploader>
  <publicdate>2023-05-30 15:45:57</publicdate>
  <addeddate>2023-05-30 15:45:57</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20230530154648[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
  <year>2024</year>
  <year>2023</year>
</metadata>
